

#### **Kelly Huynh**

Relationship Manager at Vietnam Industry Research and Consultancy

Connect

**♠** Message

More...



Try Premium Free for 1 Month

# stay positive

#### Connect

**△** Message

• • •

Kelly Huynh · 3rd

Relationship Manager at Vietnam Industry Research and Consultancy

Vietnam · 500+ connections · Contact info



Vietnam Industry Research and

Consultancy



Hoa Sen University (Not for Profit)

People and pages related to Kelly

See all



>



**American Chemical Society** 

Page • Non-profit Organization Management 117,603 followers

#### **Follow**



Page • Research 247,436 followers

#### **Follow**



Novartis Institutes for BioMedical Research (NIBR)

Page • Pharmaceuticals 155,595 followers

**Follow** 

#### About

Experienced Corporate Communications with a demonstrated history of working in the education management industry. Skilled in Client Relationship, Corporate Communications and Customer Care. Strong sales professional with a Bachelor's degree focused in Business English from Hoa Sen University, Viet Nam.

#### Activity

5,597 followers



IMPORTANCE OF COMPETITOR IDENTIFICATION Partner/competito...

Kelly shared this



Hạnh Phúc là Sẻ Chia

#### See all activity

#### Experience

#### **Relationship Manager**



/ietnam Industry Research and Consultancy · Full-time May 2018 - Present

SCIC Building 16 Truong Dinh, District 3, HCM City, Viet Nam

VIRAC was founded by professionals who have research skills and several years of work experience with prestigious and leading organizations, both locally and globally, such as D&B (Dun & Bradstreet) or Experian as well as local banks and financial institutions.

We are experts in the production of a wide range of reports, especially Company and Industry reports of most industries and all companies registered in Vietnam, with such comprehensive analysis as business risks analysis, company position, prospects and in-depth views like ownership structure, financial statements, markets and operation.

We assist our clients including Investors, Banks, Financial Organizations, Managers and etc. in making strategic decisions, which has positive impacts on their operations, by providing quality reports and analysis with deep insights. ... see more

#### **KTDC Group- IELTS Office**

3 yrs 9 mos



Personal Assistant to Managing Directors

Full-time

Aug 2016 - May 2018

· 1 yr 10 mos

151 Nguyen Dinh Chieu, District 3, HCM City, Viet Nam

Assist Managing Director incorporating strategy, ensure department meets its goals and secure the effective operation of our business.

#### **Corporate Sales Executive**

Full-time

Sep 2014 - May 2018

· 3 yrs 9 mos

151 Nguyen Dinh Chieu, District 3, HCM City, Viet Nam

Responsible for creating advantageous relationships with corporate clients to build and maintain corporate sales accounts.

#### **HR Specialist**

AAA Pharmaceutical Inc · Full-time

Mar 2014 – Sep 2014

- · 7 mos
- Received recruitment orders from management
- Worked with HR solutions company such as: Vietnamworks, timviecnhanh.com... to upload recruitment announcement
- Contacted candidates and arranged interview schedules
- Reported all HR issues and activities to BOD

... see more

#### **Teaching Assistant**

POLY Foreign Language Center · Part-time Aug 2012 – Mar 2014 · 1 yr 8 mos Vietnam

#### Education

#### Hoa Sen University (Not for Profit)

3achelor's degree, Business English 2010 – 2014

Activities and Societies: Step Up - English competitions of eloquence

## TOEIC IG Vietname

	Skills & endorsements
	Customer Service . 7
	<b>Tobias P. Dreesman and 6 connections</b> have given endorsements for this skill
	Corporate Communications . 5
	Peter Fleming and 4 connections have given endorsements for this skill
	English . 4
	Tu Nguyenanh and 3 connections have given endorsements for this skill
	Industry Knowledge
	mustry knowledge
	Account Management . 2
	Online Advertising . 2
	Troubleshooting . 2
	Customer Relationship Management (CRM) . 2
	Social Media . 2
	Sales
	Business Strategy
	Strategy
	Market Research
	Future dia Dial Management
	Enterprise Risk Management

	Show less ^
Business Information	
Networking . 1	
Other Skills ②	
Negotiation	
Time Management . 1	
Teamwork . 1	
Interpersonal Skills	
Microsoft Word . 1	
PowerPoint . 1	
Microsoft Excel . 2	
Microsoft Office . 2	
Tools & Technologies	

#### Recommendations

Received (1) Given (2)



#### Sơn Nguyễn

Senior Relationship Manager at Vietnam Industry Research and Consultancy

January 17, 2019, Kelly worked with Son in the same group

Kelly's incredible adaptability with potential clients has let her excel in sales. Her great connection with the customers and relentless perseverance to always make the customer happy. Kelly is also able to work effectively with other co-workers, making her a great addition to the team. She would be an asset to... **See** 

#### Accomplishments

#### Courses

Business Writing • Professional Selling Skills

## \_

#### Languages

English • Vietnamese

#### Interests

### Meg Whitman in CEO at Quibi



2,366,101 followers

#### James Caan CBE in



Serial entrepreneur, philanthropist and former Dragon! 3,299,438 followers

#### The Economist



12,332,325 followers

## Sallie Krawcheck in CEO and Co-Founder of Ellev



CEO and Co-Founder of Ellevest 2,669,464 followers

#### Hamdi Ulukaya 🛅



Founder and CEO of Chobani 161,174 followers

#### Jessica Alba in

Founder of The Honest Company 1,751,917 followers



## People also viewed



**Lê Anh Sơn •**3rd

Researcher at Vietnam Industry Research and Consultancy

Connect



Van Anh Ho •3rd

Relationship manager at Vietnam Industry Research and Consultancy

Connect



**Duc Minh Hieu Vu •**3rd

Founder and CEO at Vietnam Industry Research and Consultancy

Connect



Nguyen Minh Phuong •3rd

Research Analyst at virac



Khanh Bich (Katie) •2nd

Recruitment Consultant ESS - Real Estate, Construction & Hospitality Industry at PERSOLKELLY Vietnam

Connect

**∨**Show more

## People you may know



BE BA (My Nguyen)

Recruitment Specialist cum Admin at Milensea Retail

Connect



Le Nhat Huy

President at UTE Logistics and Supply Chain Club

Connect



Khánh Linh Đỗ

Human Resources Assistant at Hachinet Software

Connect



Nguyen Dinh Dat

Frontend Angular Developer

Connect



Connect

**∨Show more** 



About

Accessibility

alent Solutions			
Community Guidelines			
areers			
Marketing Solutions			
Privacy & Terms 💙			
d Choices			
dvertising			
ales Solutions			
Mobile Mobile			
mall Business			
afety Center			
Questions?  (isit our Help Center.			
Manage your account and privacy to to your Settings.			
elect Language			
(Arabic) العربية			
inkedIn Corporation © 2021			
	ď		

